localbuzz.com.au 2013-05-09

# Privacy Policy : LocalBuzz!

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy applies to all personal information collected by LocalBuzz! via the internet.

LocalBuzz! recognises the importance of your privacy, and that you have a right to control how your personal information is collected and used. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that seriously. Unless you directly give us consent to do otherwise, LocalBuzz! will only collect and use your personal information as set out below.

This privacy policy applies to your use of the LocalBuzz! websites located at www.localbuzz.org, www.local-buzz.co.uk, www.localbuzz.com.au, www.localbuzz.ca, and other top-level domains relevant to different countries (collectively, the " **LocalBuzz Sites** "), but not does apply to any third party sites that may be linked to them, or any relationships you may have with the business listed on the LocalBuzz Sites.

The terms " **we** ", " **us** ", and " **LocalBuzz!** " refer to the LocalBuzz! Sites and LocalBuzz Media Ltd. The terms " **you** " and " **your** " refer to you, as a user of any of the LocalBuzz Sites. The term " **personal information** " means information that you provide to us which personally identifies you to be contacted or identified, such as your name, phone number, email address, and any other data that is tied to such information.

BY USING THE LOCALBUZZ SITES, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE LOCALBUZZ SITES.

**1\. Information We Collect and How We Use It**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the collection of personal information is limited to that which is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified below. If we use your information in a manner different than the purpose for which it is collected, then we will ask you for your consent prior to such use.

**Collection of information.** The four main ways we collect personal information about you are: 

  * when information about you is posted on a LocalBuzz! website, either by you or by a third party; 
  * when you log into a LocalBuzz! website or otherwise submit personal information to LocalBuzz!; 
  * when you use a LocalBuzz! website, in which case our system automatically collects information relating to your visit to that website, such as your IP address; and
  * through the operation of web crawlers we may use from time to time (described in more detail below).

The type of information that we collect from you may include the following: your name, phone number, address, email address, company position/title, IP address, cookies, personal information that you include in your business listing or personal information that you email/send using email functionality on the LocalBuzz! website. 

Our purpose in collecting information about you is to: 

  * provide you with a better service experience with content and advertising that is more relevant to your interests; and
  * create a business information database for use as part of LocalBuzz! online business. Whilst the LocalBuzz! business information database is designed to operate as a business directory (not a directory of individuals) it is possible that personal information may become included in the business information database.

**Account information.**  If you create an account to take advantage of the full range of services offered on the LocalBuzz Sites, we ask for and record personal information such as your name and email address. We use your email address to send you updates and news, and contact you on behalf of other users (such as other users who send you compliments, personal messages, or favorite reviews).

**Submissions.**  We store and may publicly display your submissions in order to provide the services that we offer. When we display your submissions, we do so together with your account name. The term " **submissions** " refers to the information that you submit or post to the LocalBuzz Sites for public display, such as business listings, business ratings, reviews, photos, compliments, and the information that you display as part of your account profile.

**Feedback.**  If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication.

**Personal messaging.**  In order to allow you to send and receive personal messages to other registered users of the LocalBuzz Sites, we record the messages that you send and receive using the LocalBuzz Sites' personal messaging feature.

**Activity.**  We record information relating to your use of the LocalBuzz Sites, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the LocalBuzz Sites and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the LocalBuzz Sites. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information.

**Cookies.**  We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely indentify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term " **cookies** " refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes while you are viewing the site. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. LocalBuzz Sites uses cookies to make your use of our website and services as convenient and effective as possible. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's browser. Cookies are useful to estimate our number of users and determine overall traffic patterns through our website. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the LocalBuzz Sites may not work properly or at all.

**Enforcement.**  We may use the information we collect in connection with your use of the LocalBuzz Sites (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

**2\. Transfer of Information**

**Disclosing your personal information.** LocalBuzz! will not use or disclose any information about you without your consent, unless: 

  * the use or disclosure is for one of the purposes described above or otherwise permitted by this policy;
  * it is required or permitted by law (including by relevant privacy laws);
  * we believe it necessary to provide you with a service which you have requested;
  * to protect the rights, property or personal safety of another LocalBuzz! website user, any member of the public or LocalBuzz!; or
  * any of the assets and/or operations of LocalBuzz! are being transferred to another party.

If you do not provide requested information, LocalBuzz! may not be able to provide you with access to or full use of sections of the LocalBuzz! website.

**Third Parties.** We may distribute your submissions to third parties, as permitted pursuant to our Terms of Use. The third [christian louboutin shoes](http://tiklouboutin.blog.co.uk/) parties may in turn publicly display or publish your submissions in connection with their own websites and media platforms. When we distribute your submissions to third parties, we typically include your account name (but not your personal information unless you include your personal information in your submissions).

We may share your personal information with third parties to provide you with services that we offer through the LocalBuzz Sites, conduct quality assurance testing, facilitate creation of accounts, provide technical and customer support, or provide specific services, such as synchronization of your contacts with other software applications, in accordance with your [hermes outlet](http://hermesoutlet.xp3.biz/) instructions. These third parties are required not to use your personal information other than to provide the services requested by you.

**Affiliates.** We may share your personal information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, " **Affiliates** ") that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company or our assets, that company will possess your personal information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Required Disclosure.** We may disclose your personal information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy; (c) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that we receive.

**Aggregate Information Disclosure.** We may disclose information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertising banners.

**Advertising.** LocalBuzz Sites use Google and Yahoo! to serve advertisements when you visit a LocalBuzz Site. Google and Yahoo! may use cookies in relation to your visits to LocalBuzz Sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services which may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about Google not using cookies in this way, click on [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) or type it into your browser.

**Marketing.** In seeking to give you the most worthwhile experience of our websites possible, LocalBuzz! may use your personal information to send you information and product updates about LocalBuzz! websites and services, or other products and services, or to permit other parties to send other information about products or services which may be of interest to you. 

We may contact you at any email or other address or contact point which we have collected or obtained in order to: 

  * contact you about your business listing on a LocalBuzz! website;
  * provide you with updated information about LocalBuzz! websites; or
  * provide you with other information about other products or services which you may enjoy.

If you are receiving promotional information from LocalBuzz! and do not wish to receive this information any longer, you may remove your name from our list by contacting the LocalBuzz! Privacy Officer by using the Contact Us section on the relevant LocalBuzz! website and asking to be removed from our mailing list. Please allow 30 working days for this request to be processed. 

**3\. Others' Information**

You may choose to provide us with another person's e-mail address so that person may be invited to create an account on this website. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person about the invitation. By providing us with another person's e-mail address, you represent to us that you have obtained the consent of the person concerned as regards such disclosure to us of their personal information. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above.

**4\. Storage of Information**

**Changing the information we have about you.** If at any time you wish to change personal information that is inaccurate or out of date, please contact us by using the Contact Us section on the relevant LocalBuzz! website. 

**Deleting the information we have about you.** If you wish to have your personal information deleted, please let us know in the same manner as referred to above. We will take all reasonable steps to change or delete information in response to such a request. If there is a reason that we cannot make that change or deletion, we will inform you of that reason. 

**Storage and security of your personal information.** LocalBuzz! will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. You should note that the internet is not a secure method of transmitting information and, as such, we are not responsible for the security of any information sent or received over the internet.

**Facilities.** Please note that LocalBuzz! may use overseas facilities including but not limited to in Ireland, the US, Canada, India, and Australia, to store, process or back up its information. As a result, we may transfer your personal information to our overseas facilities. However, this does not change our commitment to keep your information secure.

**4\. Links**

The LocalBuzz Sites may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

**5\. Future changes**

Our commitment to being a leading provider of online business directory services means that our business will continue to evolve as we introduce new services and features. Because of this, from time to time, our policies will be reviewed and may be revised. LocalBuzz! reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time and notify you by posting an updated version on each LocalBuzz! website. The amended Privacy Policy will apply between us whether or not we have given you specific notice of any change.
